Exclusive Seller of Eden Academy Uniforms
And... 99.5.
I'm two millimeters bigger than last time!
I'm sure it's just an error.
You never know. Kids grow up so quickly.
Indeed.
Well, with that in mind, we should probably
have your uniform made a little bigger.
But it was quite a shock to hear that
you were suddenly married, Yor.
You should have told me the
last time you were here!
I'm, er, sorry about the other day.
And to think that your lovely daughter is
going to the prestigious Eden College.
Congratulations.
Fank you very much.
Are you an Eden College alum?
Oh, no. I went to an insignificant
little school out in the country.
Oh, then do be careful.
There's something of a wall between parents
who are Eden alumni and those who aren't.
Apparently this causes discrimination and
bullying among the children, too.
Oh, and hazing from the honor students,
and conflict between the
dorm kids and commuters.
Speaking of, I hear that kidnappings
of commuter kids are on the rise.
It's not surprising, considering most of the
kids who can attend Eden are rich.
I don't wanna go to school anymore.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
Don't worry. There are plenty
of fun things about it, too.
Okay, all done with your measurements.
Let's see, you'll be getting one uniform,
plus a winter coat, a vest, and a sweater,
for three additional items.
You're a regular here, so I'll
get those done immediately.
Oh, you'll be able to get everything else
you need from the shop on the corner.
This is going to cost more than I thought.
What's the matter?
I am in fear that I will be kidnapped.
Oh, I see. You sure didn't waste any time.
Yor, is it all right if we eat out today?
Yes, of course.
Are there any kidnappers at the restaurant?
Here's our special for the day.
Pork sauté in pawpaw sauce with
porcini mushrooms and potato potage.
Po?
Looks delicious.
Must be cipher P.
Ah, a notice about my briefing.
It'll be in five days at
1300 hours at safe house D.
Understood.
But I really need to ask them to stop
using this notification method.
There's something unpleasant about it.
5 Days Later
Hello?
Oh, yes, hi.
What? It's done already?
All right. We'll come
pick up the order today.
Thank you.
Is the uniform done?
Sounds like it.
But I have my briefing today.
I'm sorry to trouble you, Yor,
but could you go pick
it up with Anya for me?
I got called into work.
Of course. You can count on me.
I might not get home until late, so you
can go ahead and get delivery for dinner.
All right.
Have a knees day.
WISE Handler
Sylvia Sherwood
Alias: Handler
Good day... or perhaps
good evening, Agent Twilight.
Hello, Handler. What's this about?
Before we get into that...
What in the world were all
those expenses the other day?!
A castle rental fee, and rental fees
for furniture to go in said castle?!
You think we're made of money?!
Oh, here's a couple more bills, actually.
Going to school is apparently very expensive.
I have to admire the balls it takes to
just casually hand me more bills.
Well, they're all necessary expenses.
Very well. Anyway...
I'm here today to brief you
on phase 2 of Operation Strix.
Though you're usually on the ball,
so that may not be necessary.
Well... I may actually
be off my game lately.
Phase 2 requires a social gathering.
Before we get into the details,
let's review how Eden works.
Eden College.
There are around 2,500 students
ranging from the ages of six to nineteen,
and the curriculum covers all thirteen years.
Academics, sports, the arts...
They offer a top-class
education in every field.
The students who manage to shine
brighter than their fellow elites
are the honor students known
as the Imperial Scholars.
The social gathering that Desmond attends
is only open to those Imperial
Scholars and their parents.
In order to become an Imperial Scholar,
a student must earn eight
merits known as "Stella."
Stella Stars are awarded for exceptional
grades and contributions to society.
Which means, first, you need to raise
your daughter into an honor student.
You may use underhanded
means if necessary.
On the other hand,
poor grades and bad behavior will result
in demerits called Tonitrus Bolts.
When a student receives eight of those,
they will be immediately expelled,
so be aware of that.
Now, let's work out the finer details.
Turning that child into a honor student...
Hello, anxiety, my old friend.
Do I look cute in my uniform?
Oh, you look absolutely adorable!
Let's go to the portrait studio later!
Ta-da!
Do I look cute?
Oh, you look absolutely adorable!
Could you leave already? How many
times are you gonna say that?
I wanna go on an ooting in this!
Yes, let's do that!
Thanks much.
Doot, do! Doot, do! Doot, do!
Why don't we stop by the park?
This is my uniform. Ta-da!
I am wearing my uniform. Ta-da!
My, your daughter's adorable.
She goes to Eden? I'm so jealous.
Oh... Hello.
Mom, I'm hungry.
And what would you like for dinner?
Hamburg steak!
So you do prefer your old mother.
I want to be with them forever.
I know that we're just a pretend family.
But...
Maybe I could be more of a mother to her.
Mama!
I just showed everyone how cute I am!
Make sure you don't dirty your
uniform before you go to school.
Say, Miss Anya. Why don't we stop
by the supermarket on our way home?
Loid said he was going to be home
late, so I'll make dinner tonight.
Ooh!
Can you cook, Mama?
Yes. I will do my very best.
Hey, is that kid from Eden?
Huh?
Is the chick next to her the mom?
She's gotta be the hired help.
No rich person's gonna
go shopping themselves.
You know, I think I want an allowance.
Me, too.
I'm sure I'll be able to make something
if I have some meat and vegetables.
I'm not sure what any of these are,
so I'll just buy all of them.
Ta-da!
I'm going outside now. I'm bored.
Oh, don't wander off too far!
Hello there, little lady.
Be a good girl for just a little bit.
Once your maid pays up, we'll let you go.
Bad guys!
Eden has bullying and kidnappings...
She was right!
I heard you can even sell their
uniforms for a sweet price.
Excellent. In that case,
little lady, let's take your—
What do you think you're doing?
Uh-oh! Looks like we're gonna have
to tack on some medical bills, too.
Let's see your wallet, Miss Hired Help.
I'm afraid I used up all of
my cash, so I have none left.
So I must ask you to leave.
I see. Then I guess we're just gonna
have to strip the little lady.
You're gonna be fired anyway,
so go back to the countryside,
you shitty little maid!
Sh-She destroyed that pumpkin
with her bare hand?!
I am that girl's mother!
If you do not want to end up like
that vegetable, leave at once!
Mama...
Are you all right?
I'm so sorry. I shouldn't have
let you out of my sight.
There, there...
And I've ruined all of the ingredients...
I'm such a failure as a mother.
But I love that my Mama
is so strong and cool.
There, there.
Killer punch, kapow!
I-I'm so embarrassed!
Mama!
Train me, please!
T-Train you?
I know it's really dangerous to
be an Eden student now.
But it won't be as scary if I train!
I can do my best at school without dying!
I wanna be like you, Mama!
Even if I can't be like a normal mother,
I'm going to do everything I can for her.
All right. Let's go straight
home and start your training.
Training!
I'm home...
Hah! Hah!
What are you doing?
Preparing her to go to school!
Hah!
Yeah... I'm filled with nothing but anxiety.
You are truly the chosen.
Due to your hard work, or perhaps your parents,
you have made it to the
hallowed halls of Eden.
To our honorable new 228 students...
Congratulations, and welcome to our school.
Everyone here at Eden welcomes you
from the bottom of our hearts.
We finally made it this far...
Papa, a lot of people are
wearing the same thing I am.
Yes. That's what a uniform is.
I still have a mountain of
problems to tackle, but...
Listen up, Twilight.
There are requirements to attend
Desmond's social gathering.
The student must be an Imperial Scholar.
And for that to happen, they
must receive plenty of merits.
Do not forget that the future of the
East and West depends on this mission.
Turning this child into an elite...
I've mostly given up on that task.
Shock!
This school is already filled
with the best of the best.
It'll be difficult to maintain a top position.
More importantly...
Next, we will announce the houses
and their housemasters.
Please come forward when
your name is called.
Class one: Specter Hall.
William Howard.
Theodore Russell.
Grace Fein.
Jessica Clark.
Next, we have class two: Cline Hall.
I wonder what class I'm gonna be in.
Who knows?
Lucy Garrett.
Actually... I do.
Because I changed parts of the
lineups to help with my mission.
Class three: Cecile Hall.
Alice Paulette.
To ensure that Anya...
Edward Perkshire.
Damian Desmond.
would be in the same class as him.
The second son of my target,
Donovan Desmond...
Damian.
That's Lord Damian to you.
He got into Eden just
like his older brother.
I've had my eye on him ever since I saw
his name on the list of students applying.
Jesse Capel.
If plan A to get Anya to become an
Imperial Scholar proves too difficult,
we'll go to plan B.
I call it... the Friendship Scheme.
THE FRIENDSHIP SCHEME
Step one: be in the same class
as him and become friends.
Step two: be invited to his
house and bring me along.
Come over!
Step three: direct contact with the target!
Welcome
Thank
you
I'm sure it won't actually go that easily,
but the more insurance we have, the better.
Anya Forger.
Go ahead.
Anya must have grown up around kids
her age at the orphanage for years.
I'll put my faith in her
communication skills.
That's the evil boss's kid.
What's with her?
Heh, I see.
She's already realized how
amazing I am and fallen for me.
You've got good taste, kid.
Playing hard to get, I see. Cute.
Becky Blackbell.
Geh...
Pleasure to meet you!
That's...
The daughter of the CEO of the major
military contractor, Blackbell.
What?! And behind her is the daughter
of the vice president of parliament!
And among the boys, there's the son of one
of the key members of the secret service!
Her classmates are a
treasure trove of intel!
Make sure you become friends
with all of them, Anya!
Loid gets so worked up when
it comes to his daughter.
I'm Becky! What's your name?
She looks like a baby. I guess I wouldn't
mind taking care of her a bit.
Hmph.
Those will be the 29 students in class three.
Hey!
Hello?!
And you will be under the
tutelage of Master Henderson.
Oh, it's the nice teacher.
So he didn't get fired after all.
I feel it's unfair for a housemaster
to have to teach new students,
but I guess it could've been much worse.
I'll just have to whip these rugrats
into shape like I used to.
And now, the new students will accompany their
homeroom teachers on a tour of the campus,
then head to their
respective classrooms.
During that time, there will be a meet and
greet in Tower C's lounge for the guardians.
Do your best, Anya.
You'll be on your own from here on out.
Okey-dokey!
You there! Stay in line!
I'm so worried...
It is always nerve-racking to send
them off into the world.
I totally understand.
This is the dining hall.
The best chefs will present you with
the most elegant dishes daily.
Beyond those doors is a special dining
hall reserved only for Imperial Scholars.
Anyone can become an Imperial Scholar if they
achieve elegant grades and earn eight Stella.
I trust that you will all do your best.
Yes, sir!
However, those who fall behind
will receive Tonitrus Bolts and face
punishment or expulsion, so stay on your toes.
Why are you looking at me?
Lord Damian's gonna be an
Imperial Scholar in no time!
Of course I am.
We'd expect nothing else!
I mean, my father is the head
of the National Unity Party.
Wait, really?!
Wow!
My Papa says we owe a lot
to the Desmond Group!
Silence! No private conversations!
They're so dumb.
What about you? What does your father do?
If he's important enough, I'd consider
letting you be my friend, too.
I will stay calm for the mission.
He's a sp—a feelings doctor.
Hmph. So he's just a nobody.
You're probably not that rich, either. Lame.
I wanna go play at your house.
You moron! Know your place, uggo!
This is the problem with
measly little peasants.
You're gonna get your gross
peasant germs on him! Scram!
Now is the time for me to
unleash my killer punch!
Listen carefully, Miss Anya.
Gasp!
Anyone who lets their
emotions control their fists
does not know the meaning of true strength.
If someone's just being a little mean,
being able to laugh it off
makes you the cooler, bigger girl.
A big girl!
And if you can keep a smile on
your face, fights will not happen.
Hey, stop being so pathetic.
At least say something back.
Heh. Like I care.
Heh.
H-How dare she smirk at me
like she's mocking me?!
Look at that composure!
She's so mature! Amazing!
I was wrong about her being a baby!
You're way more grown-up than
I thought. I'm impressed.
I'm a grown-up?
Heh.
Don't get cocky, you stupid uggo!
Uggo, uggo, Queen Uggo!
Lord Damian, perhaps you should
broaden your vocabulary...
What's your problem?
Sure, she's uglier than me,
but you don't have to be so mean.
Shut your mouth!
You there! How many times must I warn you?
Do you want punishments on your first day?
Curse you... How dare you
embarrass me like that?!
You'll pay for this!
Mama, you liar. Smiling didn't help at all.
If you don't quit it,
I'm gonna tell the teacher!
What? You have proof that we did it?
Yeah, yeah!
Go on. Move!
Hey, you smug uggo!
I'm gonna bully you every single day!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson so you'll
never be able to smirk again!
Her feelings doctor father might
be able to fix her if she cries.
Seriously? Well, that's impressive!
Aren't you a special widdle girl?
Hey, where do you think
you're looking? You scared?
What is the meaning of this?!
Sir! She just punched Lord Damian!
I just reached out my hand ,
and somehow, he ran into it.
You liar! You're not fooling anyone!
You were even making sure the
teacher wasn't looking earlier!
You got any proof I did it?
You left the imprint of
your fist on his face!
I trust you are aware that
perjury is a disgraceful act,
Anya Forger.
That's not what happened, sir!
She was holding back all day,
but these bullies just...
So it's true that she hit him?
Listen carefully, Miss Anya.
Gasp!
The only time it's all right for
you to use force is, for example,
if you're saving a friend in trouble.
H-Her foot...
He stepped on it.
So I got mad...
I'm sorry.
She did that for me?!
Oh, Anya!
She held back her own personal anger,
Thank you! Thank you, Anya!
and had the courage to stand
up to a lad for her friend.
I'm so moved!
Truly elegant, Anya Forger.
But I'm afraid...
So the Desmonds didn't appear after all.
Well, there's no need to rush.
Now that she's enrolled,
we have all the time in the world.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The students' orientation is now complete,
so please head toward the courtyard.
And I was able to make some connections.
If you would gather round,
we will take a group photo.
Where's Anya?
Forger.
Come with me.
She punched a boy?
Are you hurt at all?
And it just happened to be Desmond's son?
Usually, acts of violence would
immediately mean three Tonitrus Bolts...
What in the world?
But at my discretion, it became one.
That is as much as I can do.
I'm terribly sorry, Loid!
All because I trained her...
I will speak with his parents, too.
Plan A
Plan B
It's the first day of school
and she lost a point.
To top it off, her relationship with
Damian couldn't be any worse.
All right, everyone! We're taking the picture!
The family on the right over there!
Smile a little more!
Say, "Cheese!"
Stella needed to become an Imperial Scholar: 8
Tonitrus Bolts until expulsion: 7
Relationship with Damian: -100
THE TARGET'S SECOND SON